RASA POONNOTOK

Lawyer, Coordinator, Secretary

PROFILE

I'm a new lawyer who need chance to learn more and improve my lawyer skills. In the same time I want to develop the necessary skills, knowledge, and experiences that must have in working. I hope my abilities will fit your team and can improve your company together.



8/430 C BUILDING CHAMBERS ONNUT STATION, SUKHUMVIT 81 STREET, SUKHUMVIT ROAD, BANGCHAK SUB-DISTRICT, PRAKANONG DISTRICT, BANGKOK, THAILAND, 10400

KAMINRASA.K@GMAIL.COM



HTTPS://KAMINRASAK.WIXSITE.CO M/MYPORTFOLIO/PROFILE



087-5859060



EDUCATION

Sriayudhya School, 2011-2013 English-Japanese GPX:3.88

Chulalongkorn University, 2014-2018 Bachelor Degree of Law GPX:2.62

Sripratum University, 2019-2021 Master Degree of Criminal Law GPX:3.88

SKILLS

LAWYER LICENSE

ENGLISH (INTERMEDIATE)

JAPANESE (BEGINNER)

MICROSOFT OFFICE

ARTS

WRITING

CHARATERISTICS

FLEXIBLE

ENTHUSIASTIC

PATIENT

RESPONSIBLE

CREATIVE

EXPERIENCE

• Assistant Corporate Secretary, Eastern Economic Corridor (EEC) (July 2021 - Present)

My duties are following my boss's instruction such as making research (academics research, legal research), making power point slide, making info graphic, designed poster and brochure, coordinate with the participants who interested to participate in seminar and so on.

• HR Manager Assistant, VERSO International School (June 2020 - September 2020)

I am an HR assistant in set up process. I help manage data of foreigner who will be teachers. Typing contract, finding information about how to make a visa for foreigner, that will work in Thailand, communicate with all of them, and follow my boss's instruction

• Lawyer Trainee, Master Legal (September 2019 - February 2020)

This law company work in bankruptcy area, I help the seniors and support them about making documents, typing the plaints and go to civil courts and bankruptcy court to send documents thing. I support the seniors in the court as lawyer trainee. I used to go to the Legal Execution Department to participate in creditors meeting in the name of my customer's company who is BAM. My duty is response about transfer rights cases in civil court.

• Game Content Writer, EdTech Thailand (October 2018 - March 2019)

Thinking about contents follow the instructed topics, think about details and conversation in each situation. There are eight situations and I have to make characters in every situation and make a story for every character. Writing the conversation that will help customers learn how to speak English in daily life, and send my drafts to foreigners to check them.

• Coordinator, California English (August 2018 - January 2019)

My duties are setting a time table for all class, reminding both of foreign teachers and students, thinking about the concept and promotion of my school's course, and selling the course to customers.

Legal Trainee, Office of the Attorney General in Thailand (May 2017 - August 2017)
Learning the working process of public prosecutor and criminal procedure in criminal court.